JULIA SIMÓN CHICO



Contact

Address: Tres Cantos, Madrid, Spain

Phone: +34 648 05 41 41 **Email:** juliasim95@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/julia-simón-chico/

Webpage: juliasimn.github.io **Birth Date:** 08/05/1995

Languages

Spanish – native English – advanced Portuguese – medium

French - basic

I have recently finished an Erasmus Mundus Master in Image Processing and Computer Vision. Program developed during 2 years in three different universities where each semester is in each of the universities. I'm interested in artificial intelligence, deep learning and computer vision.

Education

- Erasmus Mundus Master in Image Processing and Computer Vision (2019 – 2021) Average grade: 8.7 Université de Bordeaux Universidad Autónoma de Madrid Pázmány Péter Katolikus Egytem
- Degree in Computer Engineering (2017 2021)
 Average grade: 8.39
 Universidad Autónoma de Madrid
- Degree in Telecommunications Engineering, (2013 -2019) Average grade: 7.92
 Universidad Autónoma de Madrid
- Electrical Engineering (International Exchange with CEAL) (2016)
 Pontifícia Universidade Católica do Rio de Janeiro Scholarship given by the Santander Bank (CEAL)

Complementary formation

- September 2017 Badminton Umpire Course
- March 2012 Badminton Coach Course

Projects

- Pattern Superposition on Digitally Generated Cartoons to Improve Visual Experience for Colorblind users.
- Facial Recognition Systems with Convolutional Neural Networks using ethnicity and gender information.
- Application for dataset capture and demonstration of heart rate detection algorithms through video sequences analysis.

Experience

- Information Technology Intern- 07/2018 to 08/2018 Management Solutions, Madrid, Spain
- → Internship in web development with .NET framework, using C#, SQL and ASP.NET.
- Internship in Université de Bordeaux- 02/2021 to 06/2021
- → Working with lung medical images. Using the program Slicer, Python, c++ and the specific library of itk (insight toolkit)

Awards

- Erasmus Mundus Master Scholarship, fully funded postgraduate studies.
- CEAL (Centro de Estudios de América Latina), scholarship given by the Santander Bank to study a semester in Brazil

Courses

- May 2020 Workshop: Building a R+D team in a company (Álvaro Vilegas (Nokia Bell Labs – Spain))
- April 2020 Workshop: Deep Learning for Computer Vision (Kevin Mc Guinnes & Diego Otero (Dublin City University)

Skills

- Python
- C++
- Deep Learning

- MatlabC
- JavaSQL
- TensorflowKeras

- C#
- OpenCV
- LaTeX

Soft Skills

Self-organized, teamwork, writing reports, adaptability, willingness to learn, planning, cooperation, dedication...